harley-davidson.asia 2018-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Harley-Davidson USA

### PRIVACY POLICY

**Harley-Davidson, Inc.'s Online Privacy Policy**  
**4/22/2013**

#### Welcome to Harley-Davidson  

At Harley-Davidson, your trust and loyalty are our most valued assets. The protection and proper use of the personal information you entrust to us is a responsibility we take seriously. Our primary goal in collecting your personal information is to help personalize your interactions and experiences with us. This notice explains what personal information we may collect from you, when we may collect it, how we may use it, and the choices you have regarding our use of it.

#### Harley-Davidson Commitment to your Privacy

  * What kind of information does Harley-Davidson collect and when?
  * How does Harley-Davidson use my information?
  * How does Harley-Davidson use Cookies or tracking?
  * Does Harley-Davidson share my information?
  * How do I access or change my information?
  * How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?
    * How do I Opt-In or Opt-Out of Promotional Communications?
    * Does this affect my communications with Harley-Davidson Dealers?
  * How does Harley-Davidson protect children’s privacy?
  * How do I know my personal information is secure?
  * What about links to other websites?
  * How am I updated about changes to the Harley-Davidson Privacy Notice?
  * Who do I contact with questions on the Privacy Notice?
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * How do I contact Harley-Davidson?

#### What kind of information does Harley-Davidson collect and when?

We may collect personal information from you when you visit one of our websites or stores, place an order with us online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey.

For purposes of this Notice, personal information may include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, or personal interests. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online, by phone, or in our stores. Information collected may be combined with information we acquire from our joint marketing partners or other unrelated third parties.

#### How does Harley-Davidson use my information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To personalize and enhance your experiences when you interact with Harley-Davidson
  * To enable Harley-Davidson to provide you with the highest quality experiences, products, services and motorcycles
  * To process and fulfill your orders, which includes sending you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and send you information by email, postal mail, telephone (including autodialed or pre-recorded call), text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer contests and promotions, and to respond to your requests
  * To help us learn more about your motorcycle and retail preferences
  * To help us manage and improve our websites, events, experiences, products and services
  * To update you on membership programs, benefits and services, and to enhance your membership experience
  * To enhance your ownership experience
  * To contact you if necessary, including by autodialed or pre-recorded call

You control the choice of receiving marketing information or marketing calls. For instructions on opting out, please see the section entitled, “How do I Opt-In or Opt-Out of Promotional Communications?"

#### How does Harley-Davidson use cookies or tracking?

Harley-Davidson and third-party companies we work with use tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on your behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. Harley-Davidson and these companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and other sites, as well as your interaction with our advertising and other communications, and use this information to determine which ads you see on websites and applications.

#### Does Harley-Davidson share my information?

We may share personal information within Harley-Davidson throughout the world to assist us in providing personalized experiences, offering products or services that may be of interest to you, and to process online orders and other requests. We also collect and share information with our independent dealers and Harley-Davidson Financial Services.

We may also share personal information with non-affiliated companies that provide services on our behalf. We take steps to ensure that these companies are contractually obligated to keep the personal information that we provide to them confidential and to use such information only as we permit.

We may also share personal information with non-affiliated companies that market Harley-Davidson branded products and services, or in connection with your financial obligations concerning a Harley-Davidson product or service. These companies have their own privacy practices and notices.

If we sell all or part of our business or assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your personal information to one or more third parties as part of that transaction.  
There may be instances when we disclose your personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, to respond to a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or another government agency, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against any legal claims, or when we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal activities, fraud, or to protect the safety, rights, or property of you, us, or a third party.

#### How do I access or change my information?

You can review and change certain personal information using one of our online sites (such as on harley-davidson.com). To access your information at a Harley-Davidson website, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit certain personal information in your account profile.

You can also ask us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact Harley-Davidson?"

#### How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?

Harley-Davidson wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information – such as information about special offers and marketing events – you can follow the process below:

#### How do I Opt-In or Opt-Out of Promotional Communications

If you change your mind about your current communication preferences with Harley-Davidson you can use the unsubscribe feature in a marketing email or log into your online profile account to change your preferences. You can also contact our customer service team via phone or mail as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact Harley-Davidson, Inc?"

Motorcycle owners may not opt-out of receiving warranty and recall information. Please note that when you make a business transaction with us (for example, renew HOG or Museum membership or purchase a product online) we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

Opt outs are entity specific. Opting out with respect to one entity is not automatically effective with respect to the others. For example, opting out for Harley-Davidson Motor Company does not opt you out for Harley-Davidson Financial Services.

If you ask to no longer receive promotional communications from us, we will mark your information as “do not market” and take steps to honor your request.

#### Does this affect my communications with Harley-Davidson Dealers?

Harley-Davidson dealers are independent entities. This notice does not apply to them. To change your preference with a Harley-Davidson dealer, please contact them directly

#### How does Harley-Davidson protect children’s privacy?

Harley-Davidson is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our websites are general audience sites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children.

#### How do I know my personal information is secure?

Protecting your data is of utmost importance to us. Harley-Davidson maintains physical, electronic, contractual, procedural and managerial safeguards to protect the confidentiality, integrity, security, and privacy of your personal information.

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. We also employ user authentication procedures and other preventative technologies designed to keep your data secure and protected. Access to personal information is limited to authorized Harley-Davidson personnel who require access to perform their job functions, and to authorized third parties that are contractually required to keep your information confidential and secure. Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect the information we maintain, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us.

#### What about links to other websites?

For your convenience, our websites may contain links to other companies’ sites such as authorized Harley-Davidson dealers, which may have privacy notices that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked sites. We recommend that you review the privacy notice of any site that you access through our sites.

#### How am I updated about changes to the Harley-Davidson Privacy Notice?

Who do I contact with questions on the Privacy Notice?  
As Harley-Davidson business or outside business conditions change, we may update Notice to reflect changes in our practices. We will post a revised Privacy Notice on our website as needed due to changes in our practices or as otherwise legally required.

For questions specific to our Privacy Notice, send your question or concern to:

**Email**  

**  
Regular Mail  
**Attn: Chief Privacy Officer  
3700 W. Juneau Avenue; PO Box 653  
Milwaukee, WI 53201

**Your California Privacy Rights  
**Residents of California may request a list of all third parties to which Harley-Davidson has disclosed certain personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. A California resident can request this list by contacting us by e-mail as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact Harley-Davidson?". All requests must include the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body and include the name of the Harley-Davidson website for which the request pertains, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that we will not accept requests except as designated here, and we are not responsible for notices that are not sent properly.

**How do I contact Harley-Davidson?  
**To change selections about receiving promotional communications, or to update your personal information, you can contact Harley-Davison by email, telephone, or postal mail. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Harley-Davidson. If contacting us by postal mail, please include your name and the email address or street address you used when you provided your information to Harley-Davidson.

**Email**  

**  
Customer Care via phone  
**1-800-258-2464

**Regular Mail  
**Attn: Consumer Change Request.  
3700 W. Juneau Avenue;

Milwaukee, WI 53208  

Back to Top

#### Who is Harley-Davidson?

For purposes of this Notice, Harley-Davidson is Harley-Davidson, Inc and its subsidiary and affiliate entities around the world (other than Harley-Davidson Financial Services, Inc. and its subsidiary entities). Harley-Davidson includes Harley-Davidson Motor Company and Harley-Davidson Dealer Systems.

Harley-Davidson Financial Services has its own privacy practices including its own opt-in and opt-out process. Please visit: HDFS Privacy Notice to learn more about Harley-Davidson Financial Services’ privacy practices.  
Harley-Davidson dealers operate independently from Harley-Davidson. This notice does not apply to them. Please contact the dealer or visit the dealer website to learn more about its privacy practices.

© 2001-2017  H-D.  All rights reserved.
